你完成任务了  希望你不要介意我这次给你的表的
All right, you're done. I hope you don't mind that I gave you
数据比较多  但是起决定作用的是第一个数据  所以如果我按照其它顺序给你这些数据
the larger table this time. But it depends on the first one, so it would've been
也是没有关系的  根据我提供的ContentValues对象的结构
hard to give you in any other order. I gave you the content value structure, so
只插入数据是非常简单的  然后  我们再查询数据
it's pretty easy to just insert the data. Then, we query the data back out.
如果moveToFirst()方法失败了  cursor对象是空的
[SOUND] If moveToFirst() fails, the cursor is empty, and
查询也就失败了  这里有很多的剪切复制工作  使用helper对象从数据库查询数据
the query failed. [LAUGH] Lots of cut and paste here. It is nice to fetch the DB
是非常好的方法  我们的测试并不是必须的
values using the helper for the data type, although its not strictly necessary,
因为我们知道这个测试肯定会得到预期的结果
since we know our test data is actually going to match our constrains. And
另外我们需要在这里添加一种失败的情况  如果我们的查询没有得到任何结果
there is one more failure case we need to add here, if our query doesn't return
就像这样  上面的工作就是为了创建一个数据库
any rows. And that's it. All that just to get a database and
并对它进行测试  现在让我们再运行一下测试程序
a way to test it. Now let's run the test again. Well, at
至少我们知道了所有的这些基本的东西都可以正常运行  记住了  如果没有这些测试
least we know all the basic stuff works, and just remember, without these tests,
你可能隔很长时间才能运行一次你的代码
you wouldn't have been able to run this code for a very, very long time.